Kristina Bogdanovic

Wilrijk, Antwerp kristinabg27@gmail.com +32456375349

Summary

Motivated Full Stack Software developer, skilled with JavaScript, Python, Django, and React. Actively pursuing an entry-level software developer position to contribute and grow within the field. I bring professional exposure and excellent communication skills from hospitality, customer service, and in my recent role as a web consultant. Strong in creative problem solving and a fast learner with experience in fast-paced, team-based environments.

Links

- Portfolio: https://kristinabog.github.io/portfolio/
- · LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kristinabog/

Technical Skills

- Languages: HTML, CSS/SASS, JavaScript, Python
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Libraries: ¡Query
- · Version Control: Heroku, GitHub, Git
- Frameworks: React, Django, Flask, Bootstrap

Education

Diploma in Full-Stack Software Development

Code Institute • Remote

12/2021

Graduated with a Merit. Credit-rated course by Edinburgh Napier University. Level 8 on the Scottish Credit and Qualifications Framework. Designed and developed 4 milestone projects which I was assessed on.

Bachelor in Tourism and Leisure Management

Erasmushogeschool Brussel • Brussels 09/2016

Graduated with Distinction

Work Experience

Web Consultant/Helpdesk Officer

European Dynamics • Athens

04/2022 - 06/2023

- Supported and assisted end users in Dutch
- Updated system documentation (e.g. System Functional Specifications and User Manuals)
- · Participated in end-user meetings, testing, training and support activities
- Reported test results and correct classification of possible incidents (e.g. software defects/new functionality), using the relevant tracking tools and procedures (e.g. Jira, Bugzilla & Postman API)

Customer Service Representative

Teleperformance • Athens

04/2021 - 03/2022

- Responded to End-User in requests through multiple communication channels in Dutch.
- Troubleshooted and resolved issues with the application and website
- Performed data entry and the use of software programs (e.g. Salesforce, Genesys & Amadeus)

Superyacht Stewardess

Superyachting • Mediterranean Sea

05/2018 - 09/2020

Service, housekeeping, laundry, helped out on deck with mooring procedures, drove the tender and dinghy, line handling, anchoring and navigational watches on 35 - 65 meter super yachts.

Languages

Dutch (native), English, French, Spanish, Serbian, German